LEANNE HOLMES

ENTRY-LEVEL FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Iholmes24@my.bcit.ca | Burnaby, BC | linkedin.com/in/leanne-holmes

CAREER SUMMARY

Recent graduate of a highly regarded technology program with several years of experience in the energy sector. Demonstrated history of executing projects in fast-paced environments. Organized, high attention to detail, and strong communication skills. Seeking a developer or analyst opportunity to leverage my technical background and project skills in a collaborative setting.

My project portfolio can be viewed at https://leanneholmes.github.io

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Object Oriented Programming Relational Databases and SQL Algorithms and Data Structures Software Development Lifecycle Agile Design Practices

Git Version Control

Web Application Frameworks

RESTful API's
Cloud Computing

WORK EXPERIENCE

Solutions Engineer Co-op

Trulioo, Vancouver, BC

Jan 2022 - Sep 2022

- Acted as a trusted technical advisor for Trulioo's sales team and prospective clients. Delivered product demonstrations and facilitated client trials
- Supported Account Executives throughout the pre-sales cycle using key market and technical knowledge
- Assisted with the rollout of RFP response software by developing a content library of verified responses. Greatly reduced the time required to complete RFP's and related questionnaires
- Created and tested the first edition of a technical training course for a new product release

Asset Coordinator Jun 2020 - Apr 2021

Schlumberger, Calgary, AB

- Managed assets for all field crews operating in Canada, as well as select markets in the U.S., worth up to \$350M in value.
 Maintained a real-time database containing the status and logistic movements of all assets
- Improved service level by creating resource allocation plans for upcoming operational and maintenance activities.

 Contributed to Canada becoming the second most profitable district within the Well Services division
- Performed accurate forecasting to optimize equipment availability while maintaining high utilization and low failure rates

General Field Engineer

Jul 2014 - Jun 2020

Schlumberger, Red Deer, AB

- Coordinated services and products on wellsite projects worth +\$20M. Tracked inventory, consumption and delivery of all materials provided by internal parties and third-party vendors
- Oversaw the successful development and launch of well monitoring software as the Field Champion for Canada
- Acted as crew lead for 20-person teams from multiple districts. Consistently delivered against monthly objectives for safety and service quality performance

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer Systems Technology

Jan 2021 - May 2023

British Columbia Institute of Technology, Burnaby, BC

Bachelor's of Science in Chemical Engineering

Sep 2009 - May 2014

University of Alberta, Edmonton, AB